[Music]
when i first learned about the product i
was pleasantly surprised to know it is
quite simple to understand
[Music]
so one the future protect benefit
simplifies critical units coverage terms
by eliminating a finite list of critical
illnesses seen in traditional insurance
plans
two it future proves our coverage by
including illnesses that are yet to be
discovered by medical science
and three the icing on the cake the
recovery program now ten thousand
dollars may not seem like much but
without it some of us may be hesitant to
seek additional assistance such as grief
counselling or home nursing
[Music]
yes it's quite good for those who are
concerned about their health so most
people do not wake up in the morning
thinking hmm what should i be buying for
critical illness insurance
for those who are serious about
reviewing their coverage i shared with
them recover first and how he stacks up
against the other planes the feedback
has been positive with most saying that
the price point is competitive and
features are also comprehensive
there is no such thing as a
one-size-fits-all insurance policy
ask insightful questions about other
options to find out how they compare to
the ones recommended to you
ask yourself am i being told only about
the benefits or do i also know the
potential drawbacks
[Music]